Guide to the Maud Slye Papers 1910s-1930s
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Cancer and Other Illness Records
  - General cancer list, vol VIII (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - General cancer list, vol IX (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - General cancer list, vol X (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - General cancer list, vol XII (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - General cancer list, vol XIII (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - General cancer list, vol XIV (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - General cancer list, vol XV (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - General cancer list, vol XVI (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - General cancer list, vol XVII (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - General cancer list, vol XVIII (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - General cancer list, vol XIX (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - General cancer list, vol XX (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - General cancer list, vol XXI (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - General cancer list, vol XXII (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - General cancer list, vol XXIII (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - General cancer list, vol XXIV (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - General cancer list, vol XXV (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - General cancer list, volXXVI (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Tumor location in mammary gland system (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Tumor locations in subaxillary mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Tumor locations in multiple mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Tumor locations in anterior mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Tumor locations in axillary mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Tumor locations in inguinal mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Tumor locations in flank mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Tumor locations in dorsal mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Round cell sarcoma, mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Alveolar sarcoma mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Mammary gland tumors in males (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Tumor types in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Metastatic growths from mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Metastatic growths from mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Metastatic growths from mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Metastatic growths from mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Metastatic growths from mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Metastatic growths from mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Metastatic growths from mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Metastatic growths from mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Metastatic growths from mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Metastatic growths from mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Cysts in mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Mammary gland (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - 3rd 10,000, 12 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - 3rd 10,000, 5 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - 3rd 10,000, 10 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - 3rd 10,000, 31 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - 3rd 10,000, 89-98 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - 3rd 10,000, 206-237 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - 3rd 10,000, 797-805 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - 3rd 10,000, 696-769 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Lung tumors (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - Primary lung tumors 1 - 363 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Primary lung tumors 501 - 600 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Primary lung tumors 364 - 500 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Primary lung tumors 601 - 670 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Primary lung tumors 671 - 725 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Primary lung adenomas C, 1 - 100 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Primary lung adenomas D, 1 - 100 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Primary lung adenomas D, 101 - 200 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Primary lung adenomas type E, 1 - 100 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Primary lung carcinoma A (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Primary lung carcinoma B (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Primary lung carcinoma B (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Primary lung carcinoma type C (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Primary lung tumors type A (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Primary lung tumors type D (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Primary lung tumors sarcomas (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Metastatic ossification and bone marrow in lungs (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Precancerous nodules in lungs (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Precancerous inflammation (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Abscesses (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Amyloidosis (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Adenoma (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - General list of adenomas vol I (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Broken bones (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Chronic dermatitis (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Cysts in glands (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Hemorrhagic ovary (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Cysts in kidney (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Cysts in lung (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Cysts in uterus (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Subcutaneous cysts (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - General list of endotheliomas (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Eye condition (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Hematomas (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Hodgkin's disease (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Abdominal hemorrhage (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Gastric hemorrhage (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Heart (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Thoracic hemorrhage (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Retroperitoneal hemorrhage (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Endothelial hyperplasias (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Lymphois hyderplasias (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Puerperal infection (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Congenitally small kidney (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Lymphoid hyperplasia (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Leukemia, 1 - 100 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Leukemia, 101 - 200 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Aberrant liver tissue (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Penduculated liver lobe (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Simple cysts in liver (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Lymphosarcoma, 1 - 100 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Lymposarcoma, 101 - 200 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - M Disease (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Mastitis, acute and chronic (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Leukemia (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Kidney metastases (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Lung metastases (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Lymph gland metastases (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Nephritis (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - General list of mesotheliomas (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - No diagnosis (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Pneumonia (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Prolapsed rectum (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Pseudoleukemia, 1- 100 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Pseudoleukemia, 101 - 200 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Pseudoleukemia, 201 - 300 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Pseudoleukemia (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Overgrown and irregular teeth (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Overgrown and irregular teeth w/out tumor (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Rupture of the ventricle (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Extra toes (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Trauma, hyperplasias, etc. (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Tyzzer disease (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Summary eye tumors (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Summary of primary lung tumors (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Summary of mammary gland tumors (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Tumors of the omentum (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Summary of skin tumors (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Grand summary of tumors (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Adrenal tumors (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Tumors of the arm (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Tumors of the sides (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Tumors of the back (dorsal aspect) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Tumors of the ventral aspect (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Tumors of the thoracic wall (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Tumors of the abdominal wall (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Pelvic tumor (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Brain (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Carcinoma (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Carcinomas, general list (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Carcinomas, special list (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Primary tumors of the diaphragm (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Tumor emboli (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Tumors of the eye (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Tumors of the fatty tissues (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Primary tumors of the rectum (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Primary tumors of the esophagus (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Primary tumors of the stomach (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Primary tumors of the intestines (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Tumors of the hand (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Tumors of the head (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Tumors of the face and muzzle (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Tumors of the lip and mouth (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Tumors of the tissues about ear (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Tumors of the eyelids (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Tumors of the jaw (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Tumors of the hip (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Tumors of the jaw (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Tumors of the jaw (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Tumors of the jaw (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Primary kidney tumors (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Tumors of the knee (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Tumors of the leg (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Tumors of the posterior limbs (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Liver tumors, 1 - 100 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Liver tumors, 101 - 200 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Primary tumors of lymph nodes (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Mesenteric primary tumors (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Mixed tumors (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Tumors of the neck (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Primary tumors of the omentum (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Primary tumors of the ovary (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Primary tumors of the pancreas (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Primary tumors of the parotid gland (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Peritoneal tumors (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Primary tumors of preputial gland (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Tumors of the prostate (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Primary retroperitoneal tumors (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Retrorectal tumors (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Tumors of the ribs (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Sarcomas, general list (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Sarcoma (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Oval and round cell sarcomas (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Seminal vesicle tumors (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Tumors of the shoulder (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Primary tumors of the skin (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Tumors of the spinal column (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Tumors of the spleen (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Primary tumors of the subcutaneous tissues and muscles (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Tumors of the tail (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Primary tumors of the testicle (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Primary tumors of the thymus and mediastinal (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Primary tumors of the thyroid (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Urinary bladder (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Primary tumors of the uterus (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Tumors of the vagina (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Tumors of the vulva (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Uncategorized (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Squamous cell carc.lung (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - General cancer list, VOIXI, 1001 - 1100 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Autopsy and Histology Reports
  - Autopsy records, rats, guinea pigs, rabbits, etc. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified records (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 1 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 3 - 4 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 5 - 6 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 7 - 8 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 9 - 9a (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 10 - 11 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 11 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 12 - 13 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 14 - 15 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 16 - 17 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 18 - 19 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 20 - 21 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 22 - 23 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 24 - 25 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 26 - 27 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 28 - 29 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 30 - 31 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 32 - 33 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 34 - 35 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 36 - 37 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 38 - 39 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 40 - 41 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 42 - 43 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 44 - 45 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 46 - 47 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 48 - 49 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 50 - 51 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 52 - 53 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 54 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 55 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 56 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 57 - 58 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 59 - 60 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 61 - 62 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 63 - 64 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 65 - 66 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 67 - 68 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 69 - 70 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 71 - 72 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 73 - 74 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 75 - 76 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 77 - 78 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 79 - 80 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 81 - 82 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 83 - 84 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 85 - 86 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 87 - 88 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 89 - 90 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 91 - 92 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 93 - 94 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 95 - 96 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 97 - 98 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 99 - 100 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 101 - 102 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 103 - 104 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 105 - 106 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 107 - 108 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 109 - 110 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 111 - 112 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 113 - 114 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 115 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 116 - 117 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 118 - 119 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 120 - 121 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 122 - 123 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 124 - 125 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 126 - 127 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 128 - 129 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 130 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 131 - 132 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 133 - 134 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 135 - 136 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 137 - 138 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 139 - 140 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 141 - 142 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 143 - 144 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 145 - 146 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 147 - 148 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 149 - 150 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 151 - 152 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 153 - 154 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 155 - 156 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 157 - 158 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 159 - 160 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 161 - 162 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 163 - 164 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 165 - 166 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 167 - 168 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 169 - 170 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 171 - 172 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 173 - 174 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 175 - 176 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 177 - 178 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 179 - 180 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 181 - 182 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 183 - 184 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 185 - 186 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 187 - 188 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 189 - 190 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 191 - 192 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 193 - 194 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 195 - 196 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 197 - 198 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 199 - 200 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 201 - 202 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 203 - 204 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 205 - 206 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 207 - 208 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 209 - 210 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 211 - 212 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 213 - 214 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 215 - 216 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 217 - 218 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 219 - 220 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 221 - 222 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 223 - 224 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 225 - 226 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 227 - 228 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 229 - 230 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 231 - 232 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 233 - 234 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 235 - 236 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 237 - 238 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 239 - 240 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 241 - 242 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 243 - 244 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 245 - 246 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 247 - 248 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 249 - 250 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 251 - 252 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 253 - 254 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 255 - 256 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 257 - 258 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 259 - 260 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 261 - 262 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 263 - 264 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 265 - 266 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 267 - 268 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 269 - 270 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 271 - 272 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 273 - 274 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 275 - 276 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 277 - 278 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 279 - 280 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 281 - 282 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 283 - 284 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 285 - 286 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 287 - 288 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 289 - 290 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 291 - 292 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 293 - 294 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 295 - 296 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 297 - 298 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 299 - 230 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 301 - 302 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 303 - 304 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 305 - 306 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 307 - 308 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 309 - 310 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Autopsy records, vol. 311 - 312 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Histology, vol. 1 - 2 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Histology, vol. 3 - 4 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Histology, vol. 5 - 6 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Histology, vol. 7 - 8 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Histology, vol. 9 - 10 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Histology, vol. 11 - 12 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Histology, vol. 13 - 14 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Histology, vol. 15 - 16 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Histology, vol. 17 - 18 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Histology, vol. 19 - 20 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Histology, vol. 21 - 22 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Histology, vol. 23 - 24 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Histology, vol. 25 - 26 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Histology, vol. 27 - 28 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Histology, vol. 29 - 30 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Histology, vol. 31 - 32 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Histology, vol. 33 - 34 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Histology, vol. 35 - 36 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Histology, vol. 37 - 38 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Histology, vol. 39 - 40 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Histology, vol. 41 - 42 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Histology, vol. 43 - 44 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Histology, vol. 45 - 46 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Histology, vol. 47 - 48 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Additional histology records (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Autopsy records, extra volume (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Series V: Notes, Articles, and Correspondence
  - Notes on MxB, BxM (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Report on MxB, BxM (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Report on lung carcinoma and leukemic disease (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Report on breast carcinoma (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Report on lung carcinoma and adenoma (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Report on spindle-cell sarcoma (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Additional reports on malignancies (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Reports on breast carcinoma (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Notes and charts (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Charts and report on origin-strain (85 - 405)xWQy8 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Articles by A. Lacassagne (French), 1933, 1935 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - John Bittner, "Spontaneous Lung Carcinoma in Mice," 1939 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Notes (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Notes (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Notecards (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Notecards (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - "Genetic Control of Type and Site of Malignancy and of the Age Incidence of Malignancy" (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - "General Discussion of Strain Seven and Breeding Records of the Charted Family Br. II E/F" (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - "The Relation of Heredity to Cancer Occurrence as Shown in Strain 73," American Journal of Cancer, July 1933 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - "Studies in the Nature and Inheritability of Cancer," The University Record XII, January 1926 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - "The Relation of Heredity to the Occurrence of Spontaneous Leukemia, Pseudoleukemia, Lymphosarcoma, and Allied Diseases in Mice," American Journal of Cancer, July 1931 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - "The Interrelation Between Hereditary Predisposition and External Factors in Causation of Cancer," Annals of Surgery, January 1931 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - "Cancer and Heredity," 1929 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1926 - 1933 (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Series VI: Oversize
  - Schematic Outline 7y2 x WQy8 (Box 55, Folder 1)